Noel Phyllis Birkby Papers, 1932-1994
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES III. ARCHITECTURE
  - Projects, OVERSIZE
    - Barber, Brooklyn, NY: sketches, elevations, plans, renderings, sections, c. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bay Ridge Medical Center, 68th St., 3rd Ave. & Senator St., Brooklyn, NY: interior elevations and details, wall sections, 1961, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bellevue Environs study: rendering, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bellomo, 7455 Soundview Ave., Southold, NY: elevations (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bondini's Restaurant, 62 West 9th St., New York, NY: floor plans, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Boulevard East housing/office complex, West New York, NJ: plans, section, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bronx Children's Psychiatric Center, Adolescent Day Treatment Center, 1180 Rev. James Polite Blvd., Bronx, NY, FDC # 3166: elevations, plans, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bronx Psychiatric Center, Community Residence, 2747 University Ave., Bronx, NY, FDC # 4722: elevations, plans, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Cardamon Lane Housing, Little Ferry, NJ: elevations, plans, sections, 1983-84 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Cinnamon Court Housing, [original name Ginger Gardens], Little Ferry, NJ: elevations, plans, sections, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Dale's Footworks, University Towne Center, San Diego, CA elevations, plans, sections, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - DeSalvo, 138 West 120th St., New York, NY: plans, 1984-85 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - East Islip Housing, Hollins Lane and Lavender Lane, East Islip, NY: details, elevations, plans, sections, rendering, 1985-86 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Fox/Whitby, 3 Sheridan Sq., New York, NY: kitchen renovation, terrace enclosure: elevations, plans, sketches, rendering, 1986-87 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Fox/Whitby, Springy Banks Rd., E. Hampton, NY: details, elevations, plans, sections, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Great Neck Elderly Housing, 700 Middle Neck Rd., Great Neck, NY: details, elevations, plans, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Hayden/Maris, 8318 Riopath, ?, CA: elevations, plans, schematic, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Jacobs, 51 8th Ave., Sea Cliff, NY: elevations, plans, sketches, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Johnson, 231 East 77th St., New York, NY: plans, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Johnston, Cutchogue, Southold, NY: elevations, plans, sketches, 1984-85 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Krogius, Lopers Path, Southampton, NY: elevations, plans, sections, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Leeds, Sagaponack, NY: sketches, section/plan/elevation, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Leser, 129 West 12th St., New York, NY: elevations, plans, sketches, 1962-63 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Lobel, Hedges Bank Drive, E. Hampton, NY: sketches, 1975-77 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Lobel, Hedges Bank Drive, E. Hampton, NY: First design--details, elevations, plans, sections, 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Lobel, Hedges Bank Drive, E. Hampton, NY: Second design-- elevations, plans, sections, 1976-77 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Long Island University, Brooklyn Campus, Library/Learning Center: plans, sections, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Long Island University, Brooklyn Campus, Modernization Program, Connolly Hall and Metcalfe Building: elevations, details, plans, sections, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Maple Knoll Village, Springdale, OH: details, elevations, plans, sections, 1978-81 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Midwood Drive Housing, Plainview, NY: elevations, plans, sections, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Pilgrim Psychiatric Center: accessibility retrofit for various buildings: plans, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Pilgrim Psychiatric Center, Community Residence, 201 Garden Place, W. Hempstead, NY, FDC #4846: details, elevations, plans, sections, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Pilgrim Psychiatric Center, Community Residence, 3531 Oceanside Rd., Oceanside, NY, FDC #4845: details, elevations, plans, sections, sketches, 1990-92 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Plandome Heights Housing, Plandome Heights, NY, Residences A and B: details, elevations, plans, sections, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Rodriguez, 235 and 195 Bergen St., Brooklyn, NY: plans, sketches, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - St. Ann's School, Pierrepont St., Brooklyn, NY, Childrens' Art Center: plans, sketches, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Sokolow, Winding Rd., Ardsley, NY: elevations, plans, sketches, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Spyer, 2 Fifth Ave., New York, NY and 254 Tuckahoe Lane, So. Hampton, NY: details, elevations, plans, sections, sketches, 1986-87 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Thursh, 239 Piermont Ave., Piermont, NY: plan, sketch, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Urban Homesteading Assistance Board, Single Room Occupancy residence, 334-336 Bergen St., Brooklyn, NY: plans, sections, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Vaughan, 201 West 138th St., New York, NY
      - Sketches, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - Details, elevations, plans, sections, 1985-87, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Wallace, 1058-1068 Pacific St., Brooklyn, NY: elevations, plans, sections, 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Watering Place Resort Hotel, Roatan, Honduras
      - Sketches, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Elevations, plans, sections, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Waterside Houses, east midtown Manhattan, NY: elevations, plans, sketches, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Witten, Barter's Island, Boothbay, ME: sketches, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Women's Hall of Fame/Women's Rights National Historical Park, Seneca Falls, NY: competition submission
      - Competition announcement, existing conditions, c. 1987 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - renderings, plans, sketches, c. 1987 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Subject files
    - General, miscellaneous, 1966-92, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 265)
    - Accessibility, 1980-91, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 266)
    - Alternative construction systems
      - General, 1970, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 267)
      - Adobe, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 268)
      - Earth-sheltered housing, 1979-80 (Box 17, Folder 269)
      - Mobile homes, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 270)
      - Self-help techniques, 1968-74, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 271)
      - Solar, 1979, 1986, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 272)
    - Architecture and Environmental Design education, 1969-78, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 273)
    - Communities, planned, 1977-78, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 274)
    - Congregate/Cooperative housing, 1978-80, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 275)
    - Environmental and community design, 1976-84, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 276)
    - Expo '70, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 277)
    - Housing, philosophy/psychology of, 1963-78, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 278-279)
    - Individuals
      - General, 1967-79 (Box 18, Folder 280)
      - Julia Morgan, 1974-76, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 281)
      - Theodate Pope Riddle, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 282)
      - Moshe Safdie, 1967-71, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 283)
      - Emily Anne Smith, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 284)
      - Paolo Soleri
        - 1966-71, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 285-286)
        - notebook "Archologies," n.d. (Box 18, Folder 287)
    - Single-parent housing, 1978-79, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 288)
    - Urban housing, 1968, 1977, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 289)
    - Women
      - Women and architecture, miscellaneous, 1948-92, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 290-291)
      - Alliance of Women in Architecture, 1972-87, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 292-295)
      - Archive of Women in Architecture, Architectural League of New York
        - General, 1973-77, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 296)
        - Exhibit "Women in American Architecture: A Historic and Contemporary Perspective," 1977-78 (Box 19, Folder 297)
      - Association of Women in Architecture, 1978-81 (Box 19, Folder 298)
      - Organization of Women Architects, 1974-75 (Box 19, Folder 299)
      - Status of women in the architecture profession, 1973-82, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 300-301)
      - Union Internationale des Femme Architectes, 1979-82 (Box 19, Folder 302)
      - Women and communities, 1978, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 303)
      - Women and environmental design, 1974-77 (Box 19, Folder 304)
      - Women and environmental design, 1980, 1985, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 305)
      - Women and housing, 1976-84, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 306)
      - Women's Architectural Review Movement, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 307)
- SERIES IV. RESEARCH, SPEAKING, AND WRITING
  - General
    - Autobiographical
      - "Creative Personal Interactions Journal," from Actualizations Workshop, c. May 1984 (Box 21, Folder 308)
      - Notes on dreams, 1979, 1990, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 309)
      - Problem solving, 1971-79, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 310-311)
      - Women in architecture, personal notes, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 312)
    - AMAZON EXPEDITION: A LESBIAN FEMINIST ANTHOLOGY edited by NPB, Bertha Harris, Jill Johnston, Esther Newton, and Jane O'Wyatt. Times Change Press, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 313)
    - Elderly Housing
      [see also notebook from Scandinavia trip 1981 and grants German Marshall Fund]
      - Notes, flyer for lecture, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 314)
      - Subject files, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 315-317)
    - "Jill Johnston," draft, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 318)
    - "Over, on and Under Water: Three Astounding Structural Systems," DESIGN AND ENVIRONMENT, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 319)
    - "Saigon: Hue, 1973" poster for slide-lecture, 4 Apr 1975 (Box 21, Folder 320)
  - Women and the Built Environment
    - Published Writings
      - "Amazon Architecture," COWRIE LESBIAN/FEMINIST, Vol. 2, No.1, Apr 1974 (Box 21, Folder 321)
        [see also tapes]
      - "Designing for the Messiness of Life," MS, Feb 1981
        - Text (Box 21, Folder 322)
        - Notes and drafts (Box 21, Folder 323)
      - "Feminist Fantasy Architecture," (with Leslie Kanes Weisman) WOMEN'S AGENDA, Vol. 2, No. 3, Mar 1977 (Box 21, Folder 324)
      - "Herspace," HERESIES II, Vol. 3, No. 3, 1981
        - Text (Box 21, Folder 325)
        - Notes, drafts, correspondence (Box 21, Folder 326)
      - "I Want it to help, not hinder me: Neue Erfahrung in Umgang mit Raum. Die 'Women's School of Planning and Architecture,' USA," ARCH+ 56, Apr 1981
        - Text (Box 21, Folder 327)
        - Notes, drafts, correspondence (Box 21, Folder 328)
      - "Patritecture and Feminist Fantasies," (with LK Weisman) LIBERATION, Vol. 19, Nos. 8 & 9, spring 1976: text, drafts, correspondence (Box 22, Folder 329)
      - "A Woman Built Environment," (with LK Weisman) QUEST, Vol. II, No. 1, summer 1975: text, drafts, correspondence (Box 22, Folder 330)
      - "Women's Community Design," illustration for 1974 calendar (Box 22, Folder 331)
      - "Women's Fantasy Environments: Notes on a Project in Progress," (with LK Weisman) HERESIES, May 1977
        - Text (Box 22, Folder 332)
        - Notes, drafts, correspondence (Box 22, Folder 333)
      - "The Women's School of Planning and Architecture," (with LK Weisman) in LEARNING OUR WAY: ESSAYS IN FEMINIST EDUCATION, 1983: text, correspondence, proofs, revisions, contracts, 1978-83 (Box 22, Folder 334)
    - Lectures, Workshops, Conferences
      - Clippings, 1974-79, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 335)
      - Correspondence, flyers, publicity, 1974-93, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 336)
      - Women in Architecture Symposium, Washington University, St. Louis, MO, Mar 1974: correspondence (Box 22, Folder 337)
      - "Women in Architecture" lecture at University of Detroit, 10 Oct 1974 (Box 22, Folder 338)
      - Gay Academic Union Conference, New York University, New York, NY, Nov 1974. "Negotiating Space: The Woman-Built Environment": correspondence, program, notes (Box 22, Folder 339)
      - Women in Design: The Next Decade conference, Women's Building, Los Angeles, CA, 20 & 21 Mar 1975: correspondence (Box 22, Folder 340)
      - West Coast Women's Design Conference, University of Oregon, Eugene, OR, Apr 1975: corr, proceedings (Box 22, Folder 341)
      - Women in Design and Planning Conference, Boston Architectural Center, Boston, MA, 7-9 Nov 1975. "Women's School of Planning and Architecture" and "Women's Fantasy Environments": program, notes (Box 22, Folder 342)
      - Gay Academic Union Conference, 28-29 Nov 1975. "Utopias--Radical Future Visions": program (Box 22, Folder 343)
      - Women in Architecture: Realizations and Possibilities symposium, Brooklyn Museum, Brooklyn, NY, Mar 1977. "How Women Experience, Conceptualize and Design Space": program (Box 22, Folder 344)
      - Alternative Educational Environments conference, Environmental Design Research Association, 1978: workshop proposal (Box 22, Folder 345)
      - Feminist Visions of the Future conference, California State University, Chico, CA, Mar 1979. "Fantasies and Realities: Women's Visions of the Built Environment": correspondence, planning materials, program, 1978-79 (Box 22, Folder 346)
      - If Women Planned the World....: Fourth Annual Women in Planning and Government Conference, University of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA, May 1979, "Alternative Design": clippings, correspondence, program (Box 22, Folder 347)
      - Fifth International Congress: Union Internationale des Femmes Architectes, Seattle, WA, Oct 1979. "Fantasy and Reality: Women's Creative Imagination": abstract, text, notes, program (Box 22, Folder 348)
      - International Festival of Women Artists, Copenhagen, Denmark, Jul 1980. "Women in Education" panel: correspondence, notes, program (Box 22, Folder 349)
      - Amerika Haus, Berlin, Germany, Jul 1980 and Sarah Kulturzentrum Cafe fur Frauen, Stuttgart, Aug, 1980. "Feminism and Architecture in the USA": flyers (Box 22, Folder 350)
      - Hexenstudientage Frauenseminar, Aachen, Germany, 24-26 Oct 1980. "Women's School of Planning and Architecture": clipping, program, publication (Box 22, Folder 351)
      - School of Architecture seminar, Aarhus, Denmark, 31 Aug-1 Sep, 1981. "Women's Fantasies in Space and Architecture": correspondence, invitation (Box 22, Folder 352)
      - Nordic Women's Building and Planning Forum, Rodhus Klit, Denmark, Aug 1981. "En arkitektskola for kvinnor": correspondence, program, report (Box 22, Folder 353)
      - Notebook from 1981 trip to Denmark, Sweden, Norway, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 354)
      - Women's Worlds: Strategies for Empowerment, Second International Interdisciplinary Congress on Women, Groningen, the Netherlands, Apr 1984. "Women and Housing: Future Visions": correspondence, program, notes, abstract, conference materials (Box 23, Folder 355)
      - A Celebration of the Beguines, New York, NY, Oct 19??. "Creating Spiritual Space for Ourselves": flyer, program (Box 23, Folder 356)
      - Kvinner, Natur, Rom conference, Oslo, Norway, Mar 1984. Workshop: program (Box 23, Folder 357)
      - Miscellaneous notes, outlines, text, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 358)
    - Research project
      - Descriptions of project, 1975, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 359)
      - Correspondence re project, 1970-82, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 360)
    - Curriculum proposals
      - "Women and the Built Environment"
        - Text, 1976, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 361)
        - Participants' Exposition entry, ACSA/AIA/NEA/UNebraska Non-Graphic Section, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 362)
        - Correspondence, 1974-75 (Box 23, Folder 363)
        - Miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 364)
        - Goddard/Cambridge Graduate Program in Social Change, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 365)
      - "Women and the Built Environment: Personal, Social and Professional Perceptions," c. 1976 (Box 23, Folder 366)
    - Fantasy drawings
      - Originals, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 367)
      - Copies, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 368)
    - Book Proposals
      - With Leslie Kanes Weisman
        - "Women's Environmental Fantasies," n.d. (Box 23, Folder 369)
        - "Women's Environmental Visions and Fantasies," 1978 (Box 23, Folder 370)
        - "Drawings of Women's Fantasies: An Environmental Investigation," n.d. (Box 23, Folder 371)
        - "Rooms of Our Own: Women's Fantasies and Realities in the Built Environment," n.d. (Box 24, Folder 372)
      - "Breaking Out of the Rectangle: Women's Fantasies and Realities in the Built Environment," c. 1980 (Box 24, Folder 373)
      - Correspondence, 1976-79, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 374)
      - Copyright issues, Birkby vs. Weisman: notes, correspondence, agreement, 1977-91, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 375)
      - Drafts, notes, lists, outlines, 1974, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 376)
      - Personal notes, 1980, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 377-382)
    - Women's Vernacular Architecture and Buildings for Women
      - General notes, flyers, 1976, 1983, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 383)
      - M.F. Beal, spiral house, Seal Rock, OR: correspondence, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 384)
      - Califa Community, Angelus Oaks, CA: flyers, 1977, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 385)
      - Danner House Women's Centre, Copenhagen, Denmark: flyer, notes, correspondence, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 386)
      - Laurie Davis and Rain Parrish: interview notes, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 387)
      - Virginia Gray, adobe tree house, Santa Fe, NM: interview transcript, floor plan, notes, photocopies of photographs, correspondence, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 388)
      - Isla Vista (CA) Tipi Village: clippings, interview notes, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 389)
      - Joyce Johnston, recycled dwelling, Truro, MA: clipping, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 390)
      - LESBIAN LAND ed. by Joyce Cheney. Word Weavers Press, 1985. (Box 24, Folder 391)
      - Nourishing Space, Vail, AZ: newsletters, flyer, 1977-78,n.d. (Box 24, Folder 392)
      - Marsha Oliver, oval house, Taos, NM: interview notes, correspondence, general, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 393)
      - Pagoda Temple of Love, Saint Augustine, FL: flyers, newsletters, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 394)
      - Anita Rodriguez, Santa Fe, NM: interview notes, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 395)
      - Sarah Kulturzentrum Cafe fur Frauen, Stuttgart, Germany: clipping, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 396)
      - Ann Stokes A STUDIO OF ONE'S OWN, ed. by Dolores Klaich. Naiad Press, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 397)
      - Tye Farm, communal dwellings and barns, Albion, CA: clipping, interview notes, 1974, 1978, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 398)
      - Wholeo, stained glass dome by Caroling, Monte Rio, CA: interview notes, color photocopies of photographs, clippings, correspondence, 1977-82 (Box 25, Folder 399)
    - Grant Proposals
      - Miscellaneous, 1973, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 400)
      - National Endowment for the Arts, 1975. "An Audio-visual investigation of the design environment as it specifically effects women." (Box 25, Folder 401)
      - National Endowment for the Arts, 1979. Project fellowship in Architecture, Planning and Design (Box 25, Folder 402)
      - German Marshall Fund Short-term Travel Award, 1981: correspondence, report (Box 25, Folder 403)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1981. "Toward the humanization of the built environment: Women's sensibilities in Architecture and Planning" (Box 25, Folder 404)
    - Subject Files
      - Articles, papers, 1971-78, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 405-406)
      - Denmark
        - General, 1980, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 407)
        - "Pa Vej: Women's Expressions on the Environment" an exhibit in Copenhagen Town Hall,: booklet, publicity, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 408)
      - Germany: clippings, reports, 1980-81 (Box 25, Folder 409)
      - Norway: conference materials, 1979, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 410)
      - Sweden: clippings, pamphlets, 1976-77, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 411)
- SERIES V. TEACHING
  - General, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 412-413)
  - Reference materials, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 414)
  - Applications for employment, 1974-91, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 415-418)
  - Applications for employment, references, 1979-88 (Box 26, Folder 419)
  - Freelance, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 420)
  - California State Polytechnic University
    - General, 1976-77 (Box 26, Folder 421)
    - Course materials, 1977-78 (Box 26, Folder 422)
  - City College of the City University of New York, School of Architecture
    - Correspondence, minutes, 1972-75, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 423-424)
    - Course materials, Architecture 121, 1972-73, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 425)
    - Course materials, Architecture 131, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 426)
  - Detroit, University of, School of Architecture: correspondence, teaching materials, student research report, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 427)
  - Hofstra University: sample of student work, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 428)
  - Los Angeles Community Design Center: general and course materials, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 429)
  - New York Institute of Technology, Center for Architecture
    - General, correspondence, minutes, 1982-90, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 430-431)
    - Architectural Drawing Manual, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 432)
    - Course materials (Box 27)
      - ARCH 6031 and 6032, Design Fundamentals I & II
        - Meetings and general, 1982-87 (Box 27, Folder 433)
        - Student work, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 434)
      - ARCH 6031, Design Fundamentals I: teaching materials,student work
        - Summer, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 435)
        - Fall, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 436)
        - Fall, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 437)
        - Fall, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 438)
        - undated (Box 27, Folder 439)
      - ARCH 6032, Design Fundamentals II: teaching materials, student work
        - Spring, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 440)
        - Spring, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 441)
        - Spring, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 442)
        - Spring, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 443)
        - Fall, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 444)
        - Spring, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 445)
        - Fall, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 446)
        - Spring, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 447)
        - undated (Box 28, Folder 448)
      - ARCH 6149, Building Construction I: teaching materials, student work
        - Teaching materials, 1987-88, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 449)
        - Student work, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 450)
      - ARCH 6175, Architectural Design I, 1983-87, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 451)
      - ARCH 6176, Architectural Design II, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 452)
      - ARCH 6217, Architectural Design IV, 1989-91, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 453)
      - ARCH 6218, Architectural Design V, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 454)
      - ARCH 6219, Architectural Design VI, 1990-91 (Box 28, Folder 455)
      - ARCH 6493, Construction Drawings I, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 456)
      - ARCH 6901, Architectural Design VII, Berlin Wall Thesis Studio
        - General, 1987-88 (Box 28, Folder 457)
        - Trip to Berlin, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 458)
        - Student work, Emelito M. Felix, 1987-88 (Box 28, Folder 459)
        - Student work, Ray Maggiore, 1987-88 (Box 28, Folder 460)
        - Student work, Brad Schneider, 1987-88 (Box 28, Folder 461)
        - Reference material, 1977-87, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 462)
        - Reference material: postcards, flyers, 1987, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 463)
        - Reference material: street maps, 1986-87, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 464)
      - ARCH 8450, Interior Design Problems II: teachingmaterials, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 465)
  - Pratt Institute, School of Architecture
    - General, 1974-78 (Box 29, Folder 466)
    - Teaching materials
      - 1972-73 (Box 29, Folder 467)
      - Elderly housing, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 468)
      - 1975-76 (Box 29, Folder 469)
      - 1977, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 470)
  - Southern California Institute of Architecture, 1977-78 (Box 29, Folder 471)
  - Southern California, University of
    - General and notes, 1978-80, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 472)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1978-80, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 473)
    - Course materials
      - ARCH 102, First Year Design
        - Fall, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 474)
        - Spring, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 475)
        - Fall, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 476)
        - Spring, 1980, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 477)
      - ARCH 105, Architectural communications media, 1978-80 (Box 29, Folder 478)
  - Womanschool Adult Education Center, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 479)
  - Women's School of Planning and Architecture
    - Bibliography, reading lists, 1977, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 480)
    - Teaching materials, 1975-78, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 481)
- SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES
  - Individuals